Jolaosho AbdulBateen

Full-Stack Developer

Summary

I am experienced in the IT Fields as a Full-stack developer. Having worked with different companies and as a freelancer, I can boldly work productively on any task I see within my capabilities. I tend to see through events and problems making me a great problem solver. As an entrepreneur, I believe I don't know everything but I can learn anything

Experience

❖ Web Developer (Part-time)

BIZZ ON IT Services

Oct 2021 - present (1 month)

- Updating previous Front-End designs
- Worked on Laravel projects relating to School Management Systems.
- Software Developer(shareholder)

TechieHealth Pharmacy

May 2021 - present (5 months)

- Configure inventory Management Systems
- Worked with other developers to maintain websites and software
- Convert UI designs to front-end
- Full-Stack Developer (co-founder)

Techlava Softwares

Sep 2020 – present (1 year 1 month)

- Creating and implementing ERD Models
- Worked with other developers to ensure client's satisfaction.
- Supervise other Front-end developers
- Implementation and integration of APIs
- Full-Stack Developer (part-time)

CoveITWorld

Oct 2021 - present (1 month)

- Working on client-based projects
- Worked with other developers to ensure client's satisfaction.

Education

Federal University of Agriculture Abeokuta

B.S.C Mechatronics Engineering

September 2019 - present (2 years)

Contact

- 12, BaytuSalaam, Accord, Ogun, Nigeria.
- +2349066299190

bataino.ronaldo@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/bataino-ronaldo

github.com/bataino

Skills

- PHP
- Laravel
- JavaScript
- JQuery
- Vue
- Ionic
- Java
- Spring Boot
- CSS
- Python
- Git & Github
- MYSQL
- SQLITE
- POSTGRESQL
- Firebase

Languages

- English (Professional)
- (Conversational) العربي